

### CONTACT

# **STATEMENT**

alienk703@gmail.com 703 399 6134

kimandy.net github.com/alienk703 Full stack developer and design enthusiast with a sensitivity to the user experience. Creative technologist who inspires and motivates others to achieve success. Laser-focused commitment to meet and exceed goals to develop responsive and functional web applications.

### **SKILLS**

# **EDUCATION**

Ruby, Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, jQuery Backbone.js, PostgreSQL AJAX, CSS & HTML

Object Oriented Programing TDD/EDD, API Integration Wireframing, Data Modeling, Photoshop & Illustrator

Fluent in Korean and Japanese

GENERAL ASSEMBLY (2014)

Web Development Immersive

Full-stack web development program focused on common best practices in object-oriented programming, MVC frameworks, data modeling, and test-driven development. Developed a portfolio of individually focused and collaboratively focused projects.

# TEMPLE UNIVERSITY (2004~2009) Bachelor of Arts

Broadcasting Telecommunication Mass Media Concentration, Music Industry Philadelphia, PA

Washington DC

### **INTERESTS**

### **EXPERIENCE**

Music Production, Bass Guitar, Movies Fantasy Sports Sports Spectating MBC TV NEWS (2012~2014)

Associate News Producer

- \* Coordinated credentials, interviews, news transcriptions, video research news research and office administration
- \* Filmed and edited video footage using ENG camera equipment

#### EMPIRE ENTERTAINMENT JAPAN (2008~2012)

Tokyo, Japan

Washington DC

Special Events Producer/Graphic Designer

- \* Produced various events to include: seminars, product launch, corporate parties, fashion show, live performances
- \* Designed event posters, invitations, flyers, PowerPoints and Keynote presentations
- \* Managed event budgeting, coordination and special talent casting